Edward U. Condon Papers 1920-1974 Mss.B.C752
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1920-1974; 128 boxes, 64 linear feet
  - Testimonial Dinner, April 1948, 3 folders (Box 116)
  - Texas Christian University (Box 116)
  - Textile Research Institute, Inc. (Box 116)
  - Theory of Proton Proton Interaction (Box 116)
  - Thom, Victor L. (Box 116)
  - Thomas, H. A. (Box 116)
  - Thomas, Lloyd E. (Box 116)
  - Thomas, Richard N. (Box 116)
  - Stellar Atmosphere, Thomas, Richard N. (Box 116)
  - Thompson, Carroll W. (Box 116)
  - Thompson, John P. (Box 116)
  - Thor Publishing Company (Box 116)
  - Thornton, Wayne H. (Box 116)
  - Thum, E. E. (Box 116)
  - Thurnauer, Hans (Box 116)
  - Thwaite, Walter E., Jr. (Box 116)
  - Tichvinsky, L. M. (Box 116)
  - Tillich, Paul. (Box 116)
  - TIME (Box 116)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 116)
  - Tinti, Alexander (Box 116)
  - Tippo, Oswald (Box 116)
  - Titz, Milos (Box 116)
  - Tolman, Carl (Box 116)
  - Tolman, Richard C. (Box 116)
  - Tompkins, C. B. (Box 116)
  - Tonks, Lewi (Box 116)
  - Science Policy as a Focus of Academic Study, Toulmin, Stephen (Box 116)
  - Townsend, J. (Box 116)
  - Trager, Frank N. (Box 116)
  - Trial by Newspaper (Box 116)
  - Tribus, Myron (Box 116)
  - Trinity Cathedral [Pittsburgh, Pa.] (Box 116)
  - Trip to Europe, 1963, 3 folders (Box 117)
  - Trip to India, 1950, 11 folders (Box 117)
  - Trip to Mexico, 1950, 3 folders (Box 117)
  - Trip to Russia, 1945 (Box 117)
  - Troupe, R. A. (Box 117)
  - Trout, James C. (Box 117)
  - Troutman Insurance Company (Box 117)
  - Trow, William Clark (Box 117)
  - Truman, Harry S., 3 folders (Box 117)
  - Truman, Harry S. Inaugural Committee (Box 117)
  - Harry S. Truman Library (Box 117)
  - Tschudy, William (Box 117)
  - Tukey, H. B. (Box 117)
  - Turner, Louis A. (Box 117)
  - Turner, Robert (Box 117)
  - Tuttle, Amanda (Box 117)
  - Tuve, Merle A. (Box 117)
  - Twitchell, Dory and Archie (Box 117)
  - U Thant, 2 folders (Box 117)
  - UFOs (Box 117)
    See: Unidentified Flying Objects
  - Ullman, John E. (Box 117)
  - Underhill, Jean W. (Box 117)
  - UNESCO Conference on Popularization of Science (Box 117)
  - Unidentified - 1954, 2 folders (Box 117)
  - Unidentified, 4 folders (Box 117)
  - Unidentified Flying Objects, 9 folders (Box 117)
    See also Condon Papers Series II
  - Unidentified Flying Objects. Case Studies - Lubbock, Texas, 9 folders (Box 118)
  - Union Carbide Corporation (Box 118)
  - Union College. Board of Visitors, 2 folders (Box 118)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 3 folders (Box 118)
  - Union Radio Scientifique Internationale [International Union of Radio Science] Boulder, Col., Aug., 1957 (Box 118)
  - Unitarian Fellowship for Social Justice (Box 118)
  - Unitarian Laymen's League [Berkeley, Calif.] (Box 118)
  - Unitarian Time on KRKD (Box 118)
  - United Air Lines (Box 118)
  - United Nations (Box 118)
  - United Nations. Development Program (Box 118)
  - United Nations. Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (Box 118)
    See: UNESCO
  - United Nations. International World University (Box 118)
  - United Nations. Israel Industrial Research Centre (Box 118)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America (Box 118)
  - U. S. Appropriations Committee Stories (Box 118)
  - U. S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 7 folders (Box 118)
  - U. S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency. U. S. Senate Hearing, March 1962 (Box 118)
  - U. S. Atomic Energy Commission, 6 folders (Box 118)
  - U. S. Atomic Energy Commission. Investigation of 1949 (Box 118)
  - U. S. Civil Service Commission (Box 118)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Committee on Government Operations. (Box 118)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Special Committee on Un-American Activities, 49 folders (Box 118-119)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Annual Report, 1953 (Box 119)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Hearing, Apr.- June 1949 (Box 119)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Hearings, Sept. 1952, 2 folders (Box 119)
  - U. S. Congress. House. Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Hearings, 1952, 11 folders (Box 119-120)
  - U. S. Congress. Joint Committee on Atomic Energy, 4 folders (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Joint Committee on Atomic Energy. Soviet Atomic Espionage. (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Joint Committee on Atomic Energy. Summary - Analysis of Hearings, 1957 (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on Government Operations. Hearing, May, 1954 (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on Government Operations. Hearing, June, 1954, 3 folders (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on Rules and Administration, 4 folders (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on Rules and Administration. Hearings, July, Aug., 1949 (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary. Subcommittee on Constitutional Rights. (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary. Subcommittee on Constitutional (Box 120)
  - Rights. Hearings, April 1957: Secrecy and Science (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary. Subcommittee to Investigate the (Box 120)
  - Administration of the Internal Security Act and Other Internal Security Laws. (Box 120)
  - Hearings, March-April, 1953 (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Internal Security Committee. (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Special Committee on Atomic Energy. Hearings. Jan.-Feb., 1946, 3 folders (Box 120)
  - U. S. Congress. Senate. Special Committee on Atomic Energy. Workbook., 4 folders (Box 120)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 120)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Environmental Science Services Administration (Box 120)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Loyalty Board, 17 folders (Box 121)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Loyalty Board. Hearing - Oct., 1947, 5 folders (Box 121)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Loyalty Board. Testimony of E. U. Condon, Sept. 20, 1948, 3 folders (Box 121)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Loyalty Board. Testimony of E. U. Condon, Sept. 21, 1948, 7 folders (Box 121)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Loyalty Board. Testimony of E. U. Condon, Sept. 22, 1948, 4 folders (Box 121)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. National Bureau of Standards (NBS), 23 folders (Box 121-122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Atomic Clock Anniversary, 2 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Congratulations on Appointment, 10 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Corning Glass Works, 6 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Guest Workers (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Handbook of Physical Measurements, 8 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. NBS - Some Letters Received Following Resignation (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Patent Office (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Secretary (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Commerce. Undersecretary (Box 122)
  - U.S. Dept. of Defense. Secretary (Box 122)
  - U.S. Dept. of Defense. Secretary of the Navy, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Justice (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of Justice. Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of State (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Air Force (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior. Bureau of Reclamation (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Interior. Geological Survey (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Navy (Box 122)
  - U. S. Dept. of the Navy. Office of Naval Research (Box 122)
  - U. S. Embassy, Italy (Box 122)
  - U. S. Foreign Service, 3 folders (Box 122)
  - U. S. General Services Administration (Box 122)
  - U. S. Information Agency (Box 122)
  - U. S. Naval Ordnance Laboratory (Box 122)
  - United World Federalists, Inc., 5 folders (Box 123)
  - Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace (Box 123)
  - Universities' National Anti-War Fund, 2 folders (Box 123)
  - University Center in Virginia, Inc. (Box 123)
  - University Club [Pittsburgh, Pa.] (Box 123)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research [Boulder, Colo.] (Box 123)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 3 folders (Box 123)
  - University of California, Irvine, 5 folders (Box 123)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz (Box 123)
  - University of Chicago (Box 123)
  - University of Chicago. Center for Policy Study (Box 123)
  - University of Chicago Press (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado, 5 folders (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Board of Regents (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Chemical Physics Committee, 8 folders (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Commission on Environmental Studies, 4 folders (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Commission on Environmental Studies. The University's Response to the Environmental Crisis. (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Council on Research and Creative Work. (Box 123)
  - University of Colorado. Joint Institute for Laboratory Astrophysics, 18 folders (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. Libraries. (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. News Service (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. Personnel Data. Physics Faculty Positions, 3 folders (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. Physics and Astrophysics Faculty (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. Regency Election, 1966, 5 folders (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. Regional Computation Center (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado. The University Club (Box 124)
  - University of Colorado and Colorado Division of Commerce and Development. Advantages of the Boulder-Denver Area for the 200-300 BeV Proton Accelerator. (Box 124)
  - University of Delaware (Box 124)
  - University of Denver (Box 124)
  - University of Florida (Box 124)
  - University of Kentucky (Box 124)
  - University of Miami (Box 124)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 124)
  - University of Mississippi (Box 124)
  - University of Missouri-St. Louis (Box 124)
  - University of Oklahoma (Box 124)
  - University of Oregon (Box 124)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 124)
  - University of South Florida (Box 125)
  - University of Southern California. Marine Laboratory (Box 125)
  - University of the State of New York (Box 125)
  - University of Utah (Box 125)
  - University of Washington (Box 125)
  - University of Washington Press (Box 125)
  - University of Wisconsin (Box 125)
  - University of Wyoming (Box 125)
  - University of Wyoming. Library (Box 125)
  - Upton, Albert (Box 125)
  - Uranium Reports, 3 folders (Box 125)
  - Urey, Harold C., 2 folders (Box 125)
  - Urey, Harold C. Evidence Regarding the Origin of the Earth. (Box 125)
  - Utterson, Michele (Box 125)
  - Vaidya, W. M. (Box 125)
  - Vail, Richard B. (Box 125)
  - Valentine, Willard L. (Box 125)
  - Van Atta, Lester C. (Box 125)
  - Van Blerkom, Janet (Box 125)
  - Van Evera, B. D. (Box 125)
  - Van Sciver, W. J. (Box 125)
  - Van Vleck, John H. (Box 125)
  - Van Vleck, J[ohn] H. Bibliography (Box 125)
  - Varney, Robert N. (Box 125)
  - Veblen, Oswald (Box 125)
  - Velander, Edy (Box 125)
  - Verkler, Robert C. (Box 125)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars. Ladies Auxiliary (Box 125)
  - Vienna University (Box 125)
  - Vietnam (Box 125)
  - Villars, Clarine and Don (Box 125)
  - Villars, Don S., 2 folders (Box 125)
  - Vinogradoff, D. (Box 125)
  - Vinti, John Pascal (Box 125)
  - Virginia Law Weekly (Box 125)
  - Visiting Scientists Program in Physics (Box 125)
  - Visscher, Maurice B., 3 folders (Box 125)
  - On the Proper Role of Scientists in a Schizophrenic World, Visscher, Maurice B. (Box 125)
  - Volkov, Anatole B. (Box 125)
  - Vollrath, Richard E. (Box 125)
  - Von Laue, M. (Box 125)
  - Vournas, George C. (Box 125)
  - Wagenlander, George V. (Box 125)
  - Wainerdi, Richard E. (Box 125)
  - Wakeman, Charles B. (Box 125)
  - Walbridge, Edward (Box 125)
  - Walker, Leonard A. (Box 125)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Box 125)
  - Walls, Gordon L. (Box 125)
  - Walton, Harold F. (Box 125)
  - Walton, Jonathan (Box 125)
  - Ware, Caroline F. (Box 125)
  - Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union (Box 125)
  - Warne, Colston E. (Box 125)
  - Washington (D.C.) Academy of Sciences (Box 125)
  - Washington (D.C.) Cathedral (Box 125)
  - Washington (D.C.) Federation of Churches (Box 125)
  - Washington (D.C.) Friends Newsletter, 3 folders (Box 125)
  - Washington University, 2 folders (Box 125)
  - Washington University. Physics Dept., 6 folders (Box 125)
  - Wasson, Ray (Box 126)
  - Watford, Lilian (Box 126)
  - "The Watkins Decision of the U. S. Supreme Court, June 17, 1957" (Box 126)
  - Watson, Bernard B. (Box 126)
  - Watson, E. Massey (Box 126)
  - High-Field Superconductivity of Alloys in Porous Glass., Watson, J. H. P. (Box 126)
  - Transition Temperature of Superconducting Indium, Thallium, and Lead Grains, Watson, J. H. P. (Box 126)
  - Watson, James (Box 126)
  - Watson, Kenneth M. (Box 126)
  - Watson, W. W. (Box 126)
  - Way, Katharine (Box 126)
  - Way, Thomas J. (Box 126)
  - Wayne State University. Center for Teaching About Peace and War. (Box 126)
  - Wayne State University Press. (Box 126)
  - Weaver, A. B. (Box 126)
  - Weaver, Warren, 8 folders (Box 126)
  - Time Magazine's Report of President's Address to AAAS, Berkeley [Calif.], January 1955, Weaver, Warren (Box 126)
  - Webb, Robert W. (Box 126)
  - Weber, Louis R. (Box 126)
  - Weber, William A. (Box 126)
  - Weeks, Sinclair (Box 126)
    See: AD-X2 Battery Additive Case
  - Weinberg, Donald L. (Box 126)
  - Weiner, Charles (Box 126)
  - Weinhaus, Robert S. (Box 126)
  - Weinrebe, Joseph (Box 126)
  - Weir, Walter D. (Box 126)
  - Weiss, Andrew (Box 126)
  - Weisskopf, Victor (Box 126)
  - Weissmann, Sigmund (Box 126)
  - Weizmann Institute of Science (Box 126)
  - Wells, Arthur N. (Box 126)
  - Weltfish, Gene (Box 126)
  - Wendlandt, W. W. (Box 126)
  - Went, Frits W. (Box 126)
  - Wertheim, G. K. The Mossbauer Effect (Box 126)
  - Wesley, John. (Box 126)
  - Wesleyan University (Box 126)
  - Western Regional Science Council (Box 126)
  - [Case] Western Reserve University, 2 folders (Box 126)
  - [Case] Western Reserve University. Visiting Committee for the Biological and Physical Sciences., 5 folders (Box 126)
  - George Westinghouse Centennial Forum Advisory Committee, 6 folders (Box 126)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation (WEC) (Box 126-127)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 8 folders (Box 126-127)
    - Atomic Energy, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Concerning New Radio and Radar Developments (Box 127)
    - Detection of Metastable Ions With the Mass Spectrometer. (Box 127)
    - First Report on Nuclear Physics Investigations, 7 folders (Box 127)
    - Formation of Focussed Space-Limited Electron Beams., 5 folders (Box 127)
    - Fundamentals of Nuclear Physics (Box 127)
    - Impedance Circle Chart (Box 127)
    - Laboratory Notebook (Box 127)
    - Locator Systems (Box 127)
    - Mass Spectrometer for Gas Analysis and Research, 3 folders (Box 127)
    - Maxwell-Boltzmann Law (Box 127)
    - Patent Applications and Issued Patents (Box 127)
    - Patent Disclosures, 1937-1945, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Practical Design Calculations With Impedance Circle Chart (Box 127)
    - Radiation (Box 127)
    - Radio-active materials (Box 127)
    - Research Memorandums (Box 127)
    - Semiconductors (Box 127)
    - Statistical Analysis (Box 127)
  - Wheeler, John A. (Box 127)
  - White, Alvin M. (Box 127)
  - White, Barbara (Box 127)
  - White, Gilbert F. (Box 127)
  - White, J. E. (Box 127)
  - White, Marsh (Box 127)
  - White, Milton G. (Box 127)
  - Whitmore, B. G. (Box 127)
  - Whitney, Anita (Box 127)
  - Whitney, H. LeRoy (Box 127)
  - Whiton, Herman F. (Box 127)
  - Wiberg, Kenneth (Box 127)
  - Wichman, Eyvind H. (Box 127)
  - Neuere Probleme Der Theoretischen Physik, Wien, W., (Wilhelm), 1864-1928 (Box 127)
  - Wiesner, Jerome B. (Box 128)
  - Wigner, Eugene P. (Box 128)
  - Wild Horse Uranium Company (Box 128)
  - John Wiley & Sons, Inc., 3 folders (Box 128)
  - Wilkinson, Roger (Box 128)
  - Williams, Robert E. (Box 128)
  - Williamson, Charles O. (Box 128)
  - Willkie, Wendell L. (Box 128)
  - Wilson, Charles W., III (Box 128)
  - National Academy of Sciences and the Problem of Security Clearance, Wilson, E. Bright, (Edgar Bright), 1908-1992 (Box 128)
  - Wilson, E. Raymond (Box 128)
  - Winans, J. Gibson (Box 128)
  - Winchester, George (Box 128)
  - Cosmic Rays, Winckler, J. R. and D. J. Hofmann. (Box 128)
  - Wing, G. Milton (Box 128)
  - Winget, R. H. (Box 128)
  - Winstead, Mrs. Lee (Box 128)
  - Winston, Carl B. (Box 128)
  - Wirin, A. L. (Box 128)
  - Wittmer, --- (Box 128)
  - Wolf, Emil (Box 128)
  - Wolfe, Hugh C. (Box 128)
  - Wolfle, Dael, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - Wolkinson, Herman (Box 128)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Box 128)
  - Woo, Chia-Wei (Box 128)
  - Wood, David R. (Box 128)
  - Wood, George P. (Box 128)
  - Wood, R. W. (Box 128)
  - Wood, Ris & Hames (Box 128)
  - Woodard, George H. (Box 128)
  - Worcester Polytechnic Institute. Conference on Research Goals. Dec., 1959, 3 folders (Box 128)
  - Workman, E. John (Box 128)
  - World Affairs Conference (Box 128)
  - World Association of Parlementarians for World Government (Box 128)
  - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention (Box 128)
  - World Constitution (Box 128)
  - World Education (Box 128)
  - World Federation of Scientific Workers (Box 128)
  - World Institute Council (Box 128)
  - World University Service. Faculty Service (Box 128)
  - Worth, Bob (Box 128)
  - Wouk, Victor (Box 128)
  - Wright, Ella C. (Box 128)
  - Wright, Nancy L. (Box 128)
  - Wybourne, Brian G. (Box 128)
  - Xerox Corporation (Box 128)
  - Yale University Press, 15 folders (Box 128)
  - Yaqub, M. (Box 128)
  - Yen, William M. (Box 128)
  - Yeshiva University (Box 128)
  - Yevick, Miriam (Box 128)
  - Y.M.C.A. and Y.W.C.A. Steering Committee (Box 128)
  - Yoder, Mrs. Cordelle (Box 128)
  - Color Centers in Alkali Silicate and Borate Glasses., Yokota, Ryosuke (Box 128)
  - "You in the Twentieth Century" (Box 128)
  - Young, Earl C. (Box 128)
  - Zacharias, Jerrold R. (Box 128)
  - Zahn, Charles T. (Box 128)
  - Zare, Richard N. (Box 128)
  - Rotational Line Strengths, Zare, Richard N. (Box 128)
  - Zemansky, Mark (Box 128)
  - Zener, Clarence (Box 128)
  - Ziman, J. M. (Box 128)
  - Zworykin, V. K. (Box 128)
- Series II. Notebooks and diaries, 1922-1946; 3 boxes, 1.25 lin. foot
  Is comprised of various diaries and date books of Condon, as well as notebooks from different courses, and projects (most notably the Bikini Atoll tests).
  - Vector analysis -- Physics 220AB, 1922-1924; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Miscellany, 1922; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Summer 1924 I, 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Summer 1924 II, 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Research notes, 1940; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Russkii (notes on Russian language), 1942; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Russian history (notes on Russian language), 1942; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Combustion, 1943; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Shimantics I, 1943; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Shimantics II, 1943; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Multi-J Program, 1944; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Theory of Arcs in a magnetic field, 1944; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Theory of chains, 1944; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Operation Crossroads, 1946; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Paul and Joe Physics notes, 1946-1947; 1 vol.; Paul and Joe Condon (Box 1)
  - Cosmic Ray Symposium, Idaho Springs, Colorado, 1949; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Notes on Hardy's Pure Mathematics, ca.1940s; 1 vol.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 1)
  - Diary, 1939; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1940-1941; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1941; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1942; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1943; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1944; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1945; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diaries, 1945-1946; 3 vols.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1948; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1949; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1950; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 2)
  - Diary, 1951; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diaries, 1952; 2 vols.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diaries, 1953; 2 vols.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diaries, 1954; 2 vols.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1955; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diaries, 1956; 2 vols.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1957; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1958-1959; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1959-1960; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1961-1962; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1963-1964; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1964-1965; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1965-1966; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1966-1967; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1967-1968; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1968-1969; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1969-1970; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1970-1971; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Diary, 1971; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
  - Address book, n.d.; Condon, Edward Uhler, 1902-1974 (Box 3)
- Series III. Miscellaneous materials, 1936-1971; 2 boxes, 0.75 lin. foot
  Includes miscellaneous files added to the collection at a later date, along with a small assortment of medals awarded to Condon and identification badges.
  - Miscellaneous additions (Box 1)
    - University of Colorado. Chemical Physics Committee, 1967-1974 (Box 1)
    - Stepanek, J. E. An Engineer Scans the Developing World (Olin Lectures, Yale University), October 1-2, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Collège de France (Box 1)
    - Turkey - METU etc. (Box 1)
    - Topics in Modern Physics (Box 1)
    - JILA (Box 1)
    - JILA - Visiting Fellows Program (Box 1)
    - NBS - AID Conference, Airlie House, Va., 1-4 Feb. 1971 (Box 1)
    - Atomic Spectra Proposal to AF (Box 1)
    - NBS Spectroscopy (Kessler, Moore) (Box 1)
    - Chem. 559. Adv. Mol. Spectroscopy, Summer, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Realia (Box 2)
    - Harvard Tercentenary medal, 1936; 1 badge and medallion (Box 2)
    - MIT Radiation Laboratory photographic identification card for E. U. Condon, 1942; 1 item (Box 2)
    - MIT Radiation Laboratory photographic identification badge for E. U. Condon, ca.1942; 1 item (Box 2)
    - Westinghouse Centenary medallion, 1946; 1 medallion (Box 2)
    - U.S. Mint Annual Assay Commission, 1949; 1 medallion (Box 2)
    - Columbia University Bicentennial, 1954; 1 bronze plaque (Box 2)
    - Frederic Ives Medal, Optical Society of America, 1968; 1 medallion (Box 2)
    - Westinghouse photographic identification badge for E.U. Condon, 1 badge (Box 2)
    - National Aircraft Shows Press Club, Life membership badge, n.d.; 1 item (Box 2)
- Series IV. Photographs, 1922-1946; 1 box, 0.5 lin. foot
  Various personal and professional photographs of Condon, no detailed inventory currently available.
- Series V. UFO materials, 1922-1946; 33 boxes, 16.5 lin. feet
  Files and documents from Condon's work on Operation Blue Book for the United States Air Force. No detailed inventory currently available.
- Series VI. Printed materials, 1922-1946; 11 boxes, 5.5 lin. feet